High school sucks
Emo: The Musical is a romance, comedy film directed by Neil Triffett.
Ethan, a sullen high-school student whose life is defined by what he hates, finds love with a blindly optimistic
Christian girl Trinity, much to the annoyance of his angst-filled band mates and her evangelistic brethren.
Ethan, played by Benson Jack Anthony.
Trinity, played by Jordan Hare.
Bradley, played by Rahart Adams.
Isaac, played by Jon Prasida.
Roz, played by Lucy Barrett.
Jay, played by Ben Bennett.
Emo the Musical is a 2016 Australian musical comedy film
written and directed by Neil Triffett.
It is also the title of a 2014 short film, also directed by
Triffett, upon which the feature is based.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.